const faithMultiChoice = [
    
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["answer 1", "answer 2", "answer 3", "answer 4"],
        answer: "answer 1",
        level: "easy"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["answer 1", "answer 2", "answer 3", "answer 4"],
        answer: "answer 2",
        level: "easy"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["answer 1", "answer 2", "answer 3", "answer 4"],
        answer: "answer 3",
        level: "easy"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["answer 1", "answer 2", "answer 3", "answer 4"],
        answer: "answer 4",
        level: "intermediate"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["answer 1", "answer 2", "answer 3", "answer 4"],
        answer: "answer 1",
        level: "intermediate"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["answer 1", "answer 2", "answer 3", "answer 4"],
        answer: "answer 2",
        level: "intermediate"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["answer 1", "answer 2", "answer 3", "answer 4"],
        answer: "answer 3",
        level: "intermediate"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["answer 1", "answer 2", "answer 3", "answer 4"],
        answer: "answer 4",
        level: "difficult"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["answer 1", "answer 2", "answer 3", "answer 4"],
        answer: "answer 1",
        level: "difficult"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["answer 1", "answer 2", "answer 3", "answer 4"],
        answer: "answer 2",
        level: "difficult"
    },


  
]

export default faithMultiChoice;